Hello everyone. Good evening. Today
we're talking about the hot issue is a
concern about the medical and health
policy. The medical and health insurance
policy provides financial protection
against medical expenses due to illness
or injury.
>> Hey, hello everyone. Today we want to
present uh about the important of health
insurance in Malaysia. Let's go.
Let's chill. There's smoke.
>> Hello.
>> Hello. Feet. Yeah.
You guys.
>> Yes. Yes. We at the side of the park.
Okay. Okay.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Okay. I will wait.
Want to come to join us?
>> Sit with us.
>> Yes. Smoke.
>> Okay. It's okay. Have a smoke.
>> Give me some.
>> Wow. Long time no see.
>> So long. We last met when we were high
school.
>> Yes. 2016. Very long time.
>> Yes.
>> It's already 10 years.
>> So what you doing right now?
>> I am by myself at the coffee.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> How about you?
>> I'm doing mechanical.
>> Mechanical mechanical.
>> What do you do?
>> Right now I'm an insurance agency.
>> Oh.
>> What company do you work for?
>> I work for production. You know
production?
>> Yes. Yes. Very famous company. Big
company, right?
>> Provide a lot of benefit. If you want to
take insurance, I can give you the best
price.
>> But I already taken the insurance. Oh,
yeah.
>> Yes. Because I heard
>> Yes. insurance.
>> Yes. You don't say insurance for what?
Scam only.
>> Why you say like that? It's not about
scam. You must we can talk. I can tell
you more about benefit of insurance.
Yes. It is for your future. For me is a
very waste of money.
>> You can say like that now. But in future
you will know.
Okay. After all of our treatment and
life, you already have a diagnos of
heart disease.
>> Heart disease.
>> Yeah. Heart disease.
>> Hello. Hello F. Can I ask you about my
insurance? Um, I have a heart disease.
It cost 50,000
and
it's about I I'm not enough money to pay
but can I take insurance for smoker?
>> Okay, let me see you first. Okay. Uh,
send me the location. Okay. Bye.
>> Okay. Are you okay?
>> My heart is pain.
>> Okay.
>> How can be like this?
>> Because I smoke
to take.
>> I'm very disappointed with myself.
>> Now, what can I tell you? You can't take
any insurance because you already s if
we proceed to use to you to buy our
insurance maybe the GL can't approve.
>> Yeah. Um I have a new new information
for you.
>> Yes.
>> Um your your disease is a heart disease.
Oh my god.
>> Yeah, it's not a big number for you. Uh
it cost like 300,000 but uh luckily your
insurance company already cover you
since you already taken the insurance uh
insurance plans.
>> Oh really?
>> Yeah it's true.
>> Thank God.
>> Yeah I will uh adjust all of my
agreement and I will tell you later.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank God I already take the insurance.
If not, I will pay a high amount of bill
and I will be broke. Thank God.